=Seal of Love= (Season 1)
= ختم الحب = (الموسم الأول)
=Episode 18=
= الحلقة 18 =
Why would they meet us here?
لماذا يقابلوننا هنا؟
Is this where the wedding will be held?
هل هذا هو المكان الذي سيقام فيه الزفاف؟
I was indeed pathetic.
كنت مثيرًا للشفقة حقًا.
Beware of traps.
احذر من الفخاخ.
Hurry. Activate the Demon-trapping Formation.
عجل.  تنشيط تشكيل اصطياد الشياطين.
She just got her core and she's far weaker.
لقد حصلت للتو على جوهرها وهي أضعف بكثير.
Perfect timing to kill her.
التوقيت المثالي لقتلها.
Another dirty trick?
خدعة قذرة أخرى؟
This is all that you can do.
هذا كل ما يمكنك فعله.
Enough to kill you.
كفى لقتلك.
You?
أنت؟
It's your Thunder Strike.
إنها ضربة الرعد الخاصة بك.
With the core back, the Thunder Strike comes again for you.
مع عودة القلب ، تأتي Thunder Strike مرة أخرى من أجلك.
I'll see how you can
سأرى كيف يمكنك
get away this time.
ابتعد هذه المرة.
How did you dodge so easily?
كيف راوغت بهذه السهولة؟
You haven't recovered yet.
أنت لم تسترد عافيته بعد.
You're far weaker now.
أنت أضعف بكثير الآن.
The Thunder Strike will kill you.
ستقتلك ضربة الرعد.
So, Master,
لذا ، يا معلمة ،
I'll take the Thunder Strike for you.
سآخذ ضربة الرعد من أجلك.
You two are really affectionate.
أنتما الاثنان حنون حقا.
Yuan.
يوان.
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
Just a flesh wound.
مجرد جرح في الجسد.
You're a mere demon.
أنت مجرد شيطان.
How could Thunder Strike just give you a flesh wound?
كيف يمكن أن تسبب لك ضربة الرعد جرحًا في الجسد؟
Both of you will die.
كلاكما سيموت.
Fusheng is taking the Thunder Strike.
Fusheng يأخذ ضربة الرعد.
Ancient Demon Dragon?
التنين الشيطاني القديم؟
He is Overlord of Devils?
هو سيد الشياطين؟
Yuan.
يوان.
He doesn't have a core.
ليس لديه نواة.
Either he's too weak to have one,
إما أنه أضعف من أن يكون لديه واحدة ،
or...
أو...
He isn't a demon.
إنه ليس شيطان.
To remove the Heart Sorcery from you,
لإزالة سحر القلب منك ،
he lost the cultivation of a thousand years.
لقد خسر زراعة ألف سنة.
I'll have the Heart-eating Bug
سآخذ الحشرة الآكلة للقلب
eat up her heart bit by bit.
تأكل قلبها شيئا فشيئا.
Fusheng will only lose her power of a hundred years.
سوف تفقد Fusheng قوتها لمدة مائة عام فقط.
Now, he forcibly revealed his real body.
الآن ، كشف بالقوة عن جسده الحقيقي.
He will be doomed.
سوف يكون محكوما عليه بالفناء.
Heart Sorcery?
سحر القلب؟
So, he...
إذا هو...
Yuan?
يوان؟
Jing Yuan!
جينغ يوان!
Come down!
إهدأ!
Yuan.
يوان.
No.
رقم.
No!
رقم!
He asked for that.
طلب ذلك.
The Seal of Love?
خاتم الحب؟
♪Love and hate fade away♪
الحب والكراهية يتلاشى ♪
Xiyun?
شييون؟
♪Reincarnation is the most unpredictable♪
التناسخ هو أكثر ما لا يمكن التنبؤ به
No.
رقم.
It's impossible.
هذا مستحيل.
This time,
هذا الوقت،
I won't leave you alone.
لن أتركك بمفردك.
♪My frustrating destiny makes me fearless♪
قدري المحبط يجعلني لا أخاف
♪And able to go anywhere I want♪
♪ وقادر على الذهاب إلى أي مكان أريد ♪
(The Seal of Love activated the reincarnation channel.)
(قام The Seal of Love بتنشيط قناة التناسخ).
(Your Grace,)
(نعمتك،)
(send His Lordship to reincarnation immediately)
(أرسل سيادته إلى التناسخ على الفور)
(so that his soul will survive.)
(حتى تنجو روحه).
♪Day after day♪
♪ يوما بعد يوم ♪
♪I never forget you♪
♪ أنا لا أنساك أبدًا
Fusheng!
فوشينغ!
♪And I always remember♪
♪ ودائما أتذكر ♪
Qing Chen.
تشينغ تشن.
If anything happens to Fusheng,
إذا حدث أي شيء لفوشينغ ،
I'm gonna kill you!
سوف أقتلك!
♪Having gone through everything♪
♪ بعد أن مررت بكل شيء ♪
♪I'm hurt all over♪
♪ لقد تأذيت في كل مكان ♪
♪In the next life May everything be in peace♪
في الحياة الآخرة ، عسى أن يكون كل شيء في سلام
♪Back in the hometown Obsessions linger♪
♪ العودة في مسقط رأس الهواجس باقية ♪
♪Pursuing the skinny love I just can't get over it♪
♪ أسعى وراء الحب النحيف الذي لا يمكنني تجاوزه
♪Dying together only exists in the legend♪
الموت معًا موجود فقط في الأسطورة
♪Memories fade away♪
الذكريات تتلاشى ♪
♪Why must I be heartbroken for someone merciless♪
♪ لماذا يجب أن أكون حزينة من أجل شخص لا يرحم
♪A perfect marriage appears in the dream♪
الزواج المثالي يظهر في الحلم ♪
♪But a dream ends anyway♪
♪ لكن الحلم ينتهي على أي حال
♪The wind blows The leaves fall Be away♪
تهب الرياح الأوراق تسقط كن بعيدًا ♪
♪Dying together only exists in the legend♪
الموت معًا موجود فقط في الأسطورة
♪Memories fade away♪
الذكريات تتلاشى ♪
♪Why must I be heartbroken for someone merciless♪
♪ لماذا يجب أن أكون حزينة من أجل شخص لا يرحم
♪A perfect marriage appears in the dream♪
الزواج المثالي يظهر في الحلم ♪
♪But a dream ends anyway♪
♪ لكن الحلم ينتهي على أي حال
♪The wind blows The leaves fall Be away♪
تهب الرياح الأوراق تسقط كن بعيدًا ♪